Guide to the Rand School of Social Science Records TAM.007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Publications, 1906-1955; 113546
  - Subseries VIB: Pamphlets and Books, 1914-1954, 114065
    - Nearing, Scott. Europe and the Next War New York: Rand School of Social Science, 32pp., 1920; 114097 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:53
    - Nearing, Scott. Europe in Revolution Second Edition. New York: Rand School of Social Science, 30pp, 1920; 114096 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:54
    - Nearing, Scott. The Great Madness. A Victory for the American Plutocracy New York: Rand School of Social Science, 44pp, 1917; 114095 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:55
    - Nearing, Scott. Labor and the League of Nations With the Full Text of the Revised Covenant of the League of Nations New York: Rand School of Social Science, 47pp., 1919; 114094 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:56
    - Nearing, Scott. The Menace of Militarism. An Analysis, A Criticism, A Protest and a Demand New York: Rand School of Social Science, 52pp., 1917; 114093 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:57
    - Nearing, Scott. The One Big Union of Business New York: Rand School of Social Science, 32pp, 1920; 114092 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:58
    - Nearing, Scott. Work and Pay New York: Rand School of Social Science, 51pp, 1917; 114091 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:59
    - Oneal, James. The American Labor Party: An Interpretation New York: Rand School Press, 14pp, ca.1936; 114090 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:60
    - Oneal, James. The Austrian Civil War New York: Rand School Press, 31pp., ca.1934; 114089 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:61
    - Oneal, James. Socialism versus Bolshevism New York: Rand School Press, 27pp, 1935; 114088 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:62
    - Oneal, James. The Workers in American History Fourth Edition. New York: Rand School of Social Science, 208pp, 1921; 114087 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:63
    - Panken, Jacob. Socialism for America New York: Rand School Press, l6pp, ca.1933; 114086 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:64
    - Renan, Ernest. Identite Originelle et Separation Graduelle du Judaisme et du Christianisme. New York: Rand School of Social Science, 26pp, 1943; 114085 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:65
    - Renan, Ernest. Le Judaisme Comme Race et Comme Religion. New York: Rand School of Social Science, 29pp, 1943; 114084 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:66
    - The Salaried Man. The Story, in Two Episodes, of an Every-Day Person New York: Rand School of Social Science, 24p, 1920; 114083 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:67
    - Schaffer, Louis. Stalin's Fifth Column on Broadway New York: Rand School Press, 31pp, 1940; 114082 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:68
    - Schapiro, Theodore. The Challenge of Workers' Education New York: Rand School of Social Science, 9pp, ca.1951; 114081 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:69
    - Scott Nearing's Address to the Jury New York: Rand School of Social Science, 30pp, ca.1919; 114080 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:70
    - Should Socialism Prevail? A Debate. New York: Rand School of Social Science, 47pp, 1916; 114079 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:71
    - Should the Workers Form a Political Party of Their Own? A Debate New York: Rand School Press, 31pp, 1932; 114078 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:72
    - Shub, David and Alexander, Robert J. What Do You Know About British Labor? New York: Rand School Press, 61pp., 1946; 114077 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:73
    - Shulman, Frederick. An Appeal to Reason New York: Rand School Press, 30pp, 1941; 114076 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:74
    - Sinclair, Upton and Lyons, Eugene. Terror in Russia? Two Views New York: Rand School Press, 63pp, 1938; 114075 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:75
    - Solomon, Charles. The Albany "Trial" New York: Rand School of Social Science, 71pp, 1920; 114074 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:76
    - Trachtenberg, Alexander, ed. The American Socialists and the War. A Documentary History of the Attitude of the Socialist Party Toward War and Militarism Since the outbreak of the Great War New York: Rand School of Social Science, 48pp, 1917; 114073 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:77
    - Trade Unions in Soviet Russia. A Collection of Russian Trade Union Documents Compiled by the I.L.P. Information Committee and the Inter­national Section of the Labour Research Depart­ment New York: Rand School of Social Science, 91pp., Nov 1920; 114072 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:78
    - The Trial of Scott Nearing and the American Socialist Society New York: Rand School of Social Science, 247pp, 1919; 114071 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:79
    - Turner, John Kenneth. Hands Off Mexico New York: Rand School of Social Science, 74pp, 1920; 114070 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:80
    - Tyler, August. The United Front New York: Rand School Press, l9pp, 1933; 114069 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:81
    - Waldman, Louis. Food and the People. The Problem of the High Cost of Living in the New York Legislature New York: Rand School of Social science, 45pp, 1918; 114068 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:82
    - War Aims, Peace Terms, and the World After the War. A Joint Declaration by Democratic Socialists of Several Nationalities. New York: Rand School Press, l6pp, Jul 1941; 114067 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:83
    - Williams, Albert Rhys. The Bolsheviks and the Soviets New York: Rand School of Social Science, 48pp, 1919; 114066 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 50: Frame XIII:F:2:84
  - Subseries VIC: The American Labor Year Book, 1916-1932; 114051
    The third part of the publications series contains a complete file of The American Labor Year Book. Published from 1916 to 1932 by the Labor Research Department, The American Labor Year Book contains numerous articles and reports on all aspects of the American labor movement. The volumes in this file are arranged in chronological order. A full bibliographical citation for each volume in this part can be found in the complete reel list for this collection.
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.1, 382 pp., 1916; 114064 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 51: Frame XIII:F:3:1
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.2, 384 pp., 1917-1918; 114063 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 51: Frame XIII:F:3:2 to Frame XIII:F:3:3
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.3, 447 pp., 1919-1920 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 51: Framerame XIII:F:3:3
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.4, 454 pp., 1921-1922; 114061 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 51: Frame XIII:F:3:4
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.5, 548 pp., 1923-1924 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 51: Frame XIII:F:3:5
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.6, 488 pp., 1925; 114059 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 51: Frame XIII:F:3:6
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.7, 571 pp., 1926 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 51: Frame XIII:F:3:7
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.8, 252 pp., 1927; 114057 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 52: Frame XIII:F:3:8
    - The American Labor Year Book: Political Issues Facing American Labor, v.9, 265 pp., 1928; 114056 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 52: Frame XIII:F:3:9
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.10, 302 pp., 1929; 114055 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 52: Frame XIII:F:3:10
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.11, 283 pp., 1930; 114054 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 52: Frame XIII:F:3:11
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.12, 337 pp., 1931; 114053 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 52: Frame XIII:F:3:12
    - The American Labor Year Book, v.13, 299 pp., 1932; 114052 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 52: Frame XIII:F:3:13
  - Subseries VID: Index to Labor Articles, 1926- 1953, 113833
    The fourth part of the publications series contains the Index to Labor Articles. Originally entitled the Index to Labor Periodicals, this publication was prepared by the staff of the Rand School's Meyer London Memorial Library from December 1926 to October 1953. In each issue of the Index, there are numerous citations for articles pertaining to the American and international labor movements. It is interesting to note that many of these citations were drawn from various labor, progressive, and radical periodicals which standard reference sources, such as The Reader's Guide to Periodical Literature, neglected to cite. The Index to Labor Articles is arranged in chronological order and is complete except for three issues. It should be noted that the editor attempted to locate these missing items at other repositories, but was unable to find them. A full bibliographical citation for each volume of the Index is located in the complete reel list for this collection.
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 1, Dec 1926; 114050 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1927
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 2, Jan 1927; 114049 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 3, Feb 1927; 114048 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 4, Mar 1927; 114047 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 5, Apr 1927; 114046 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 6, May 1927; 114045 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 7, Jun 1927; 114044 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 8, Jul 1927; 114043 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 9, Aug 1927; 114042 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 10, Sep 1927; 114041 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 11, Oct 1927; 114040 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 12, Nov 1927; 114039 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 1, no. 13, Dec 1927; 114038 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 1, Jan 1928; 114037 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1928
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 2 (Lacks no. 2), Feb 1928; 114036 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 3, Mar 1928; 114035 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 4, Apr 1928; 114034 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 5, May 1928; 114033 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 6, Jun 1928; 114032 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 7, Jul 1928; 114031 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 8, Aug 1928; 114030 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 9, Sep 1928; 114029 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 10, Oct 1928; 114028 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 11, Nov 1928; 114027 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 2, no. 12, Dec 1928; 114026 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 1, Jan 1929; 114025 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1929
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 2, Feb 1929; 114024 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 3, Mar 1929; 114023 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 4, Apr 1929; 114022 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 5 (Lacks no. 5), May 1929; 114021 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 6, Jun 1929; 114020 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 7, Jul 1929-Aug 1929; 114019 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 8, Sep 1929; 114018 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 9, Oct 1929; 114017 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 10, Nov 1929; 114016 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 3, no. 11, Dec 1929; 114015 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 1, Jan 1930; 114014 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1930
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 2, Feb 1930; 114013 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 3, Mar 1930; 114012 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 4, Apr 1930; 114011 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 5, May 1930; 114010 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 6, Jun 1930-Sep 1930; 114009 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 7, Oct 1930; 114008 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 4, no. 8, Nov 1930-Dec 1930; 114007 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 1, Jan 1931; 114006 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1931
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 2, Feb 1931; 114005 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 3, Mar 1931; 114004 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 4, Apr 1931; 114003 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 5, May 1931-Jun 1931; 114002 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 6, Jul 1931-Aug 1931; 114001 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 7, Sep 1931; 114000 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 8, Oct 1931; 113999 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 9 (Lacks no. 9), Nov 1931; 113998 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 5, no. 10, Dec 1931; 113997 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 1, Jan 1932; 113996 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1932
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 2, Feb 1932; 113995 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 3, Mar 1932; 113994 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 4, Apr 1932; 113993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 5, May 1932-Jun 1932; 113992 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 6, Jul 1932-Aug 1932; 113991 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 7, Sep 1932; 113990 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 8-9, Oct 1932-Nov 1932; 113989 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 6, no. 10, Dec 1932-Jan 1933; 113988 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 1, Feb 1933; 113987 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1933
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 2, Mar 1933; 113986 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 3, Apr 1933; 113985 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 4, May 1933; 113984 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 5, Jun 1933-Jul 1933; 113983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 6, Aug 1933-Sep 1933; 113982 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 7, Oct 1933; 113981 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 8, Nov 1933; 113980 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 9, Dec 1933; 113979 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 7, no. 10, Jan 1934; 113978 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 1, Feb 1934; 113977 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1934
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 2, Mar 1934; 113976 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 3, Apr 1934; 113975 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 4, May 1934; 113974 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 5, Jun 1934-Jul 1934; 113973 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 6, Aug 1934-Sep 1934; 113972 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 7, Oct 1934; 113971 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 8, Nov 1934; 113970 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 8, no. 9, Dec 1934; 113969 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 1, Jan 1935; 113968 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1935
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 2, Feb 1935; 113967 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 3, Mar 1935; 113966 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 4, Apr 1935; 113965 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 5, May 1935; 113964 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 6, Jun 1935-Jul 1935; 113963 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 7, Aug 1935-Sep 1935; 113962 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 8, Oct 1935; 113961 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 9, Nov 1935; 113960 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 9, no. 10, Dec 1935; 113959 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 1, Jan 1936; 113958 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1936
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 2, Feb 1936; 113957 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 3, Mar 1936; 113956 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 4, Apr 1936; 113955 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 5, May 1936; 113954 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 6, Jun 1936-Jul 1936; 113953 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 7, Aug 1936-Sep 1936; 113952 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 8, Oct 1936; 113951 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 9, Nov 1936; 113950 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 10, no. 10, Dec 1936; 113949 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 1, Jan 1937; 113948 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1937
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 2, Feb 1937; 113947 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 3, Mar 1937; 113946 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 4, Apr 1937; 113945 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 5, May 1937-Jun 1937; 113944 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 6 (no. 6 was not used), undated; 113943 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 7, Jul 1937-Aug 1937; 113942 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 8, Sep 1937; 113941 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 9, Oct 1937; 113940 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 10, Nov 1937; 113939 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 11, no. 11, Dec 1937; 113938 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 1, Jan 1938; 113937 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1938
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 2, Feb 1938; 113936 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 3, Mar 1938; 113935 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 4, Apr 1938; 113934 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 5, May 1938-Jun 1938; 113933 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 6, Jul 1938-Aug 1938; 113932 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 7, Sep 1938; 113931 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 8, Oct 1938; 113930 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 9 (no. 9 was not used), undated; 113929 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 10 (no. 10 was not used), undated; 113928 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 11, Nov 1938; 113927 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 12, no. 12, Dec 1938; 113926 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 1, Jan 1939; 113925 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1939
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 2, Feb 1939; 113924 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 3, Mar 1939; 113923 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 4, Apr 1939; 113922 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 5, May 1939; 113921 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 6, Jun 1939; 113920 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 7, Jul 1939; 113919 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 8, Aug 1939; 113918 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 9, Sep 1939; 113917 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 10, Oct 1939; 113916 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 11, Nov 1939; 113915 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 13, no. 12, Dec 1939; 113914 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 1, Jan 1940; 113913 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1940
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 2, Feb 1940; 113912 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 3, Mar 1940; 113911 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 4, Apr 1940; 113910 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 5-6, May 1940-Jun 1940; 113909 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 7-8, Jul 1940-Aug 1940; 113908 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 9, Sep 1940; 113907 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 10, Oct 1940; 113906 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 11, Nov 1940; 113905 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 14, no. 12, Dec 1940; 113904 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 1, Jan 1941; 113903 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1941
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 2, Feb 1941; 113902 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 3, Mar 1941; 113901 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 4, Apr 1941; 113900 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 5-6, May 1941-Jun 1941; 113899 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 7-8, Jul 1941-Aug 1941; 113898 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 9, Sep 1941; 113897 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 10, Oct 1941; 113896 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 11, Nov 1941; 113895 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 15, no. 12, Dec 1941; 113894 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 16, no. 1-2, Jan 1942-Feb 1942; 113893 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:4:1942
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 16, no. 3-4, Mar 1942-Apr 1942; 113892 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 16, no. 5-6, May 1942-Jun 1942; 113891 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 16, no. 7-8, Jul 1942-Aug 1942; 113890 (Box 55, Folder 3)